Lombard is one of the few gainers today
apart from ltts after its earnings B
estimates yes joins in with the details
yes well Rema a strong set of numbers as
far as icsi Lombard is concerned to
start with just look at the top three
numbers the first one is net earned
premium That Grew by about 13 1.2% in
the third quarter uh the second
important number is underwriting laws
for the company that reduced by 4% in
the quarter and finally combin ratio uh
that came in about
103.6 versus 10
14.4% of course with respect to combined
ratio it is better when this number
reduces below 100 is when you're
operationally profitable uh the
management also said that if the X uh if
the catastrophe claims in the quarter
are to be reduced then the combined
ratio goes even further down uh to the
point of about 10
2.3% as far as segmental performance is
concerned that also was very strong
Health the retail health Health premium
grew by about 21% retail Health
underwriting profit came at about 2 CR
versus loss of 11 CR on a year-on-year
basis a group health premium That Grew
42% underwriting loss reduced to about
11 CR versus loss of 14 CR motor premium
though the growth was just about 2% but
the underwriting profit under the motor
segment that sort of doubled in this
particular quarter fire premium uh that
saw a degrowth of 13% but the
underwriting profit in that segment was
also down about 19% and finally Marine
premiums they grew by about 21%
underwriting profit under the Marine
segment was up 22% so of course a strong
top line for the company in third
quarter as well as stronger operational
performance coming from icsa
Lombard thank you very much for that yes
that's icsa Lombard for you we'll slip
into a break we'll come back and talk
technicals rishal malan joins in on the
other
side
[Music]